Guide to the Matt Kahn Papers SC1094 SC1094
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Personal
  - Photographs
    - Slides
      - Claire eggs/ Andts for 35th anniversary, 31048 (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Claire/ Garden/ Ochie/ Carmel/ Ti-nam (/71), 26085 (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Claire Graduation, 28277 (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Claire Graduation/ Car-rally (Fiat), Jun-1967 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - Claire (make-up) / Rite of Spring, 1973/ 1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Claire (Misc.), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - Claire (Tahoe) Long Hair, Aug-1965 (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - Claire/ Kite/ Igo sand sculpture (Winter '92), 33635 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Claire (Pueblo), 26512 (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Claire Pumpkin Patch/ Ti-nam/ Lyda, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Claire (swim) Hearst Castle, Aug-1961 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Classic cars/ Doves, 34455 (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Connie Northway Ring, Sep/Oct-1977 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Como, 30590 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Concert, 38171 (Box 6, Folder 43)
      - Copenhagen - Tivoli, Aug-1963 (Box 6, Folder 44)
      - Cordoba, 28004 (Box 6, Folder 45)
      - Cozumel, 1972, 26299 (Box 6, Folder 46)
      - Culls (Orient) (Box 6, Folder 47)
      - Crow Fetish Tops/ Chore boy/ Eggbeater/ hook/ fan / Lapiz/ Tiger earrings, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 48)
      - Cyclops (Box 6, Folder 49)
      - Cyclops (Box 6, Folder 50)
      - Danish Furniture, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 51)
      - Dark Painting 88, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 52)
      - Dark Painting (II) 88, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 53)
      - Davies Auditorium, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 54)
      - Decoration Day, 31168 (Box 6, Folder 55)
      - Desert, 30407 (Box 6, Folder 56)
      - Design Misc. (Faberge/ Leroy/ Japan packaging), 1977/ 1979 (Box 6, Folder 57)
      - Dept., 33487 (Box 6, Folder 58)
      - Design, Jul-1962 (Box 6, Folder 59)
      - Design Misc. (Telephone/ Kodak camera/ Artifacts/ Painting), 1978/ 1979 (Box 6, Folder 60)
      - Diablo K motel/ club, 26451 (Box 6, Folder 61)
      - Diaz Award, 26451 (Box 6, Folder 62)
      - Disneyland, Sep/Oct-1986 (Box 6, Folder 63)
      - D.N rings, 31382 (Box 6, Folder 64)
      - Drawings, Oct-1961 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Drawings Model/ Gaudi, 27426 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Drawings (Misc.), Jun-1968 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Dyed Hair/ Closonee, 34734 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      - Earthquake, 32782 (Box 6, Folder 69)
      - Easter - '93/ Flag + shaver containers (160), 1993 (Box 6, Folder 70)
      - Easter Eggs/ Breads/ Concrete Garden Sculpture (David), 1979 (Box 6, Folder 71)
      - Easter (tables/ clam/ Claire/ Lyda), 28216 (Box 6, Folder 72)
      - Easter '62, May-1962 (Box 6, Folder 73)
      - Easter cookies/ Jellos/ St. Mary's/ Disney, 38473 (Box 6, Folder 74)
      - Eastern trip/ Whitney/ Mus. Primitive Art/ School interiors/ MOMA (June 3-11), Jun-1960 (Box 6, Folder 75)
      - Eastern Trip (MIT/ Yale/ Chicago) (June 3-11), Jun-1960 (Box 6, Folder 76)
      - Eaves Droppers, 34060 (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Eclipse, 1979, 28887 (Box 6, Folder 78)
      - Eggs/ Zani/ Stamps, 1980/ 83/ 84 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Eichler, Jan-1961/ 2000 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Eloquent object, 32234 (Box 6, Folder 81)
      - England, Aug-1963 (Box 6, Folder 82)
      - Ethnic artifacts/ Pulley Masks figure, 33970 (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Eucalyptus leaves/ Corvette, 33258 (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Europe/ Spain, Nov-1962 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - Expo, Oct-1967 (Box 6, Folder 86)
      - Expo Bruelles, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - Expo (USA/ Britain/ France/ Czech etc.) (Box 6, Folder 88)
      - Expo ('67/ '58), 1958/ 1967 (Box 6, Folder 89)
      - Factory (Box 6, Folder 90)
      - Falconhead belts/ Moca/ Gandle stick (silver), 34759 (Box 6, Folder 91)
      - Fallen leaf/ Lake trip ('82), 30256 (Box 6, Folder 92)
      - Fam/ Ochie ('88), 32234 (Box 6, Folder 93)
      - Family (Box 6, Folder 94)
      - Family 1961, Jul-1961 (Box 6, Folder 95)
      - Family (Jule, Jess/ Gary/ Claire (hat)/ Helen, Lyda/ Claire, Lyda/ Ira (hat), Apr-1968 (Box 6, Folder 96)
      - Family (May 61), May-1961 (Box 6, Folder 97)
      - Family (Spring 69), May-1969 (Box 6, Folder 98)
      - Family Italy (Firenze, Venice), May-1963 (Box 6, Folder 99)
      - Family (Claire/ Helen/ Ira/ Ti-nam), Jul-1967 (Box 6, Folder 100)
      - Family (Jess, Julia, Ira, Mendelowitz), May-1965 (Box 6, Folder 101)
      - Farmer Project (Spring '84), 30803 (Box 6, Folder 102)
      - Fedex Wrap Bus/ X'mas bell/ U-Haul/ Ira/ SEE's, 35827 (Box 6, Folder 103)
      - Fences (Fontana + Stanford), 1962/ 65/ 66 (Box 6, Folder 104)
      - Field Day, 1962, Jun-1962 (Box 6, Folder 105)
      - Filoli, 30103 (Box 6, Folder 106)
      - Finnish Lapland Karesuando/ Lapp Flora (Box 6, Folder 107)
      - Firenze (1), 1976-89 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Firenze (2), 1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Firenze (3), 1981-84 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - Firenze (4), 1975/ 81/ 84 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - Fir/ Essay (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Firecrackers/ Fireworks/ Kites/ Portraits, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Fireworks (July 4/ 85), 31232 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Fireworks, Flag, 38231 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Flood/ Pompeii/ Herculaneum/ Spain, 28004 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Florence Verona (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Flower clusters/ Tungent Spoon/ Nose piece, 39600 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Flowers, 38108 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - France, 1959/ 70/ 81 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - France (July-66) / Brussels (Apr-76), 1966/ 76 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - France/ TVN, 29160 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - France Family, 27395 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Fresno, 2000/ 2004 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Farmer's Market, 37500 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Firg, 1999, 36373 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Friesland, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Garden, 31168 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Garden/ Halloween/ Snow/ Misc. children, Jan-1962 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Gaudi etc, 28004 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Gaudi (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Gaudi Sag. Fam. (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Gaudi (Guell Park) (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Gaudi '85 (S. Familia), 31594 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Gaudi Toledo Segovia, Nov-1962 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Gaudi '76, 28004 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Gaudi Batllo, 25781 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Gaudi Crypt, 25781 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Gaudi Guell Park, 25781 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Gaudi Guell Park, Nov-1962 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Gaudi Mila, 25781 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Gaudi (Parlav Guell + Park Guell), 25781 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Gaudi Sag. Fam./ Domenec/ Montaner/ Barcelona, 25781 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Genova/ Lake Como, 1963/ 70 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - Germany (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Giorgi Exhibit, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Glass Eggs/ Venini Plate/ Fetishes/ Benz valentine, 35916 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - GG Bridge '87, 31898 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Gorbachev, 33025 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Gorbi (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Gorbi visit '90, 33028 (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Granada, 1976, 28004 (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Grand Canyon, 31291 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      - Grand Canyon (2), 31291 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - Greece/ Turkey, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      - Green Ford/ Mosaic candy/ Eye cups/ Iron pyrite/ Xmas candy/ Kleenex/ Knives, 37987 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      - Greece, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      - Group A, 1959/60 (Box 9, Folder 51)
      - Group B (Box 9, Folder 52)
      - Group C (Box 9, Folder 53)
      - Group D (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Group E (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - Group F, 39173 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Group G, Jul-1959 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - Group H (Box 9, Folder 58)
      - Group I (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - Group J (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - Gaubino Urbino, 1996? (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - Josh Des. Synth '93, 34121 (Box 9, Folder 62)
      - Halloween, 36831 (Box 9, Folder 63)
      - Halloween 1983-84, 1983/87/88/92 (Box 9, Folder 64)
      - Halloween 1986, Nov-1986/ 67/ 71 (Box 9, Folder 65)
      - Halloween 1989, Nov-87/ 88/ 89 (Box 9, Folder 66)
      - Halloween 1992, 33909 (Box 9, Folder 67)
      - Halloween '96 (mask)/ Doves, 35431 (Box 9, Folder 68)
      - Halloween storm trooper, Oct-77/ Nov-82 (Box 9, Folder 69)
      - Hang Gliders, 33270 (Box 9, Folder 70)
      - Halloween/ Textiles + Prints/ S. Smith?, Aug-1966 (Box 9, Folder 71)
      - Hawaii, Sep-1965 (Box 9, Folder 72)
      - Hearst Pool/ Project City/ Rancho Motel Pool (Aug 1960) (Box 9, Folder 73)
      - Helsinki, 29068 (Box 9, Folder 74)
      - Hexcel/ Cars (Jaguar, Fiat), 1964/ 71 (Box 9, Folder 75)
      - Holidays '82, 30317 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Holland '58, Jan-1959 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Holland, 1963/ 65/ 66/ 75 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Holland/ Belgium '86, 31594 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Hoover dam/ Valley of fire, 30317 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Hospital, 28976 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - House, 1960-09, Sep-1960 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - House-construction, 1959, Jun-1959 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Houston (Galleria/ Rothco Chap./ Cont. Arts Museum), 28522 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - I5 Wildflowers, 33364 (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Ice, 1979, 28976 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Indian Lures/ Ruby Eggs/ Clouds/ Flowers, 33208 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - Innsbruck, Aug-1963 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - Interlachen/ Juan-Les-Pins, 25781 (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - Ira's, Apr-1966 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - Ira-Claire Easter '61, Apr-1960/ 61 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - Ira/ Kings Canyon/ Waterfalls/ Fisherman/ River, 37865 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Ira (Hawaii?), Aug/ Sep-1965 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Ira (potting)/ Claire (piano), May-1965/ 66 (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Ira graduation, Jun-1968 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Ira's kite (Spring '84)/ Pomponio, 30803 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Iris/ St. Mary's, 32599 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Iris + Tulip, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Istanbul, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Italy, Apr-1963/ Mar-1989 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Italia/ Firenze, 1963-93 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Italy (Milano, Sermione, Bologna, Torino, Urbino, Venice), 1963/ 1976 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Italy Family, Feb-1963 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      - Jeep, 1996, 35098 (Box 10, Folder 29)
      - JEK 75th birthday/ Granny Ma 75th, 26816 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      - JEK, JK halloween/ Ira orange shirt/ Balloon, Nov-1965 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      - Jewelry, 1983/ 1999 (Box 10, Folder 32)
      - Jewelry, 1960/ 1962 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      - Jewelry BRS, 26999 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      - June 65, Ira graduate/ Rings, Jun-1965 (Box 10, Folder 35)
      - Kashmir (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Kautokeino essay (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Kelly phone/ Rosh Hashowa (R.H) table, 32782 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Kings Canyon, 37865 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Kings Canyon/ People, 38131 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Kites (1964), Jun-1964 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Kites (1985), 31168 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Kites (1987 Winter), 31809 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Kites (1991-1992) #1, 1991/ 92 (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Kites (1993-1996) #2, 1993/ 96 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Kites + Fireworks ('97), 35569 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      - Kites (1998), 35827 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      - Kites (1999), 36281 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      - Kites (2001), 36951 (Box 10, Folder 49)
      - Kites (2000 + '01), 36951 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      - Kites (2001 + '04), 38108 (Box 10, Folder 51)
      - Kites (2002), 37319 (Box 10, Folder 52)
      - Kites (2003), 37653 (Box 10, Folder 53)
      - Kites (2003), 37653 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      - Kites (2008), 39508 (Box 10, Folder 55)
      - Kites (2009), 39873 (Box 10, Folder 56)
      - Kites (2008/ 09), Mar-2008/ 09 (Box 10, Folder 57)
      - Kites (2010/ 12), Aug- '10/ Jan - '12 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      - Kites (various #1), 70/ 82/ 85/ 87/ 90 (Box 10, Folder 59)
      - Kites (various #2), 73/ 77/ 82 - 87 (Box 10, Folder 60)
      - Kites + Portraits, 1965- 89 (Box 10, Folder 61)
      - Kite Surfing #1, 38231 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      - Kite Surfing #2, 38231 (Box 10, Folder 63)
      - Kites Misc., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 64)
      - Kite day '69, May-1969 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      - Knife/ Snakes/ Misc (Dove eggs/ xmas card/ fly) CK, 34820 (Box 10, Folder 66)
      - Knossos, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      - Kushi, 34121 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      - Knife/ Xams Bell/ Bumper Stickers/ Pruners/ Tanks, 36161 (Box 10, Folder 69)
      - LA Moca Fountain, 32905 (Box 10, Folder 70)
      - LA Fountain WET, 32174 (Box 10, Folder 71)
      - LA Moca Huntington, 32905 (Box 10, Folder 72)
      - LA trip/ 1996, 35096 (Box 10, Folder 73)
      - LA trip - Watts/ Disney/ SF Arca, 38473 (Box 10, Folder 74)
      - Laguna/ Rancho Detads, 31291 (Box 10, Folder 75)
      - Landscape/ Mountains, 31291 (Box 10, Folder 76)
      - Larry Ryan slides, 1985/ 86 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      - Las Vegas flight, 30621 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      - Las Vegas, 30317 (Box 10, Folder 79)
      - Lassen/ Shasta dam, Aug-1960 (Box 10, Folder 80)
      - Le Mont Saint Michel, 32325 (Box 10, Folder 81)
      - Light painting, 32143 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      - Lincoln, 36008 (Box 10, Folder 83)
      - Lisa Okada, 32295 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      - Lobos, Jun-1969 (Box 10, Folder 85)
      - Lobos (Birds/ clay/ Claire/ Lyda), 28185 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - Lobos/ Monterey/ Painting, Dec-1960 (Box 10, Folder 87)
      - Long Beach + NY, 26481 (Box 10, Folder 88)
      - London Misc. - Claire (Box 10, Folder 89)
      - London/ Ronchamp/ Vienna, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 90)
      - London/ Sweden, 29068 (Box 10, Folder 91)
      - Louvre 1989, 32325 (Box 10, Folder 92)
      - Lyda + Helen Christening, Jun-1968 (Box 10, Folder 93)
      - Lucerne Family, Aug-1963 (Box 10, Folder 94)
      - Lucerne Basel, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 95)
      - Lucerne + Munich, Aug-1963 (Box 10, Folder 96)
      - Lyda 6/80, 29403 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Lyda, 1975/ 77/ 80/ 85 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Lyda T., 28672 (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Lyda 65th birthday, 33135 (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Lyda-73/ Claire-71/ Bush Party-69/ JK Party-73, 1969/ 71/ 73 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Lyda Et Al dinner/ Lunch at Lark Creek Inn, 1983/ 90 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Lyda T. - pumpkins/ costume, 1967/ 68 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Lyda weaving (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - M.K, 29860 (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Magic Mountain, 1996, 35096 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Maggio 96 + Misc, 35217 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Magic Mountain, 2003, 37742 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Mantova/ Mazer/ Emo S.Vito, 33482 (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Majd Rakoff Bike/ Hitchcock stamp, 36069 (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Mantis Johnson, 29495 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - Marin Civic Center/ Freddy/ Blood oranges/ Dogs/ Hummingbird, 35096 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Masks/ Esquire re-run, 31686 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Masks, Rings, 38292 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Masters Project G. Priestley, Dec-1964 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Matt Kahn Garden #2, Sep-1960 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - M.K paintings, 1985/ 88/ 89 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - M.K paintings, 1956/ 75/ 84/ 95 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - M.K paintings, 1953/ 60/ 63 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - M.K paintings Set III (incomplete), 1975- 84 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - M.K (71-74), 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - M.K ('75), 27699 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - M.K art, 1978/ 79 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      - M.K Dec '89 show Stanford, 32843 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - M.K Exhibit Syntex, 27273 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Matt Kahn paintings (Fox, dunes, dawn det.), 1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      - Matt Kahn paintings (Sun god, Vox, Great ape..), 1975-78 (Box 11, Folder 31)
      - Matt Kahn Misc., 2004/ 2009 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      - Mazer, 31959 (Box 11, Folder 33)
      - Mendelowitz Pin/ Cacti/ Iceland poppings, 33695 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      - Mendocino ('97), 35674 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      - Mendocino Trip/ Ira/ snakes/ passion flowers/ bulletin board/ N.W spoon, 36008 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Mesa Verde, 31291 (Box 11, Folder 37)
      - Mexican duplicates for R.W (Box 11, Folder 38)
      - Mexico (Museum/ Zocalo/ Lagunilla market/ Masks), Jul-1965 (Box 11, Folder 39)
      - Mexico D.F, 26299 (Box 11, Folder 40)
      - Mexico - Teotihuacan/ Tula, Jul-1965 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      - Miami (3/94), 34394 (Box 11, Folder 42)
      - Micro-photos Iodine (Box 11, Folder 43)
      - Milano - 1966/ 1983, 30590 (Box 11, Folder 44)
      - Milano Venice, 1979 (Box 11, Folder 45)
      - Mimbres Spoons, 32813 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - Miri, Sjeff Lyda, Pt. Lobos, 1966/ 69 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Misc., May-1999/ 2000 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - Misc. (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - Misc. (Eucalyptus + Bones + Expo + Leaf), 31959 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - Misc. (Building/ Vicenza?), 1981 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - Misc. (Cities + Design + Nature), 1972- 82 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - Misc. (GG bridge/ Inverness/ Timber Cove/ Family), Jun-1969 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - Misc. (Clock tower), 30987 (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - Misc. (Patterns/ Nature/ Human subjects), 1985/ 98 etc (Box 11, Folder 55)
      - Misc. (Gallery), 31291 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Misc. (Personal), 1979 - 86 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - Misc. (Ira Claire Spring '62/ Knorr Church/ Eclipse), Apr-1962 (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Misc. (No label), 30987 (Box 11, Folder 59)
      - Misc. Nature (shells/ flowers/ garden/ web/ grapes), 1968/ 69/ 75 (Box 11, Folder 60)
      - Misc. Nature, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 61)
      - Misc. Nature, 26481 (Box 11, Folder 62)
      - Misc., 40544 (Box 11, Folder 63)
      - Misc. (Jewelry/ beads/ drawings), Feb-1964 (Box 11, Folder 64)
      - Miscellaneous, 1965/ 95 (Box 11, Folder 65)
      - Miscellaneous, 26755 (Box 11, Folder 66)
      - Mollie Stone's Truck (Fire Truck Dept. Rubeschi), 35704 (Box 11, Folder 67)
      - Mohet blimp/ Stanford aerial view, 29037 (Box 11, Folder 68)
      - Miscellaneous, 88/ 89/ 90 (Box 11, Folder 69)
      - Miscellaneous (Design) (Box 11, Folder 70)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976/ 93 (Box 11, Folder 71)
      - Misc. Art, Jan-1970 (Box 11, Folder 72)
      - Misc. Design (Leis Pens wood eggs/ Candy packages), 27820 (Box 11, Folder 73)
      - Misc. (Flowers/ Trees), Sep-1965 (Box 11, Folder 74)
      - Misc. Styling (Design/ Telephone), 32752 (Box 11, Folder 75)
      - Mixing bowls, 39814 (Box 11, Folder 76)
      - Motorcycles, 1998-99, Jul-98/ Aug-99 (Box 11, Folder 77)
      - Murano glass, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 78)
      - Mussels, 27515 (Box 11, Folder 79)
      - MOCA, 31778 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - MOMA (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - MOMA - Design (black + white) (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - MOMA; Manhole, 37257 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Monreale/ Paestum/ Spoleto, 1963/ 70 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Monte Alban, 26299 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Morrison Hardware/ Cambodian Box + Candle sticks, 34759 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Mother's Day/ Easter '84, May/ Jun-1984 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Mount Shasta/ Mc. Cloud River, Aug-1960 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Murano glass, 33420 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Musee D'orsay, 1988, 32325 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Mycenea, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - New Guinea Carvers (Summer '94), 34547 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Nimes, Nov-1962 (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Nimes, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - New Yorker Covers/ Mex. Boy (dupes), 34182 (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Northland (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Northway Race, 30468 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Norway Lapland, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Norway Stave Church/ Berg., 29068 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - NY ATT/ MET, 30011 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - NY Chrysler Bldg. 666, 30011 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - NY World Trade Center, 30011 (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - NY General, 30011 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - NYC Sep '87, 32021 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - National Gallery Interior (Washington D.C), 30011 (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Ochie Simon etc., Apr-1969 (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Ocotlan/ Yagul/ Mitla, 26299 (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Olympia, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Oranges '00/ Kites '07, 39142 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Oranges/ Hammers/ Halloween costumes/ cookies, 34700 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Oregon Coast/ Crater Lake/ Mendocino '75, 27607 (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - 03 L.A Disney / Concert Hall, 37742 (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Orvieto '81, 29830 (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - Orvieto, 1981/ 84 (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - Orvieto, 1981/ 84 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Orvieto (cathedral) + Herculaneum + Pompeii, 1963/ 66/ 79 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Oslo Museums, 29068 (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Ostia, 29160 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Oaxaca, Jul-1965 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Oaxaca/ Mexico/ Lobos, 26299 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Oaxaca Radish festival, 26299 (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Paestum/ Tarquinia, Apr-1963 (Box 12, Folder 43)
      - Paestum/ Pompeii/ Herculaneum, Apr-1963 (Box 12, Folder 44)
      - Painting/ Drawing, 1955 - 1969 (Box 12, Folder 45)
      - Painting, Jul-1962 (Box 12, Folder 46)
      - Paintings, 1955- 65 (Box 12, Folder 47)
      - Painting (light/ oval) (Box 12, Folder 48)
      - Paintings M.K, 1946 - 1956 (Box 12, Folder 49)
      - Paintings M.K, 1985/ 89 (Box 12, Folder 50)
      - Paintings M.K, 1943-62 (Box 12, Folder 51)
      - Paintings (UFO, Fox, Clipper etc.), 1976/ 79 (Box 12, Folder 52)
      - Paintings/ Design Duplicates, Oct-1961 (Box 12, Folder 53)
      - Paintings M.K c/o Peter Inhorf, Oct-1961 (Box 12, Folder 54)
      - Paintings (Pleasure Dome/ Bimming Moss/ Eye of god/ Fur + Feathers etc.), Jan-1962 (Box 12, Folder 55)
      - Palio '86, 31594 (Box 12, Folder 56)
      - Paris 1988, 32325 (Box 12, Folder 57)
      - Palermo/ Monreale/ Cetalu/ Siracusa/ Tarraanto/ Metaponto/ Lelle/ Casalle/ Pugnochiuso/ Laquila/ Tivoli (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Panama Gold Piece/ Moretti Plate/ Claire "Ukrainian" Egg/ Murano Eggs/ Liberty Stressed, 37288 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      - Paris #1, 1966/ 1975 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      - Paris #2, 1962/ 66/ 70/ 75 (Box 12, Folder 61)
      - Paris #3, 1966/ 75 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      - Paris/ Bern, 1962/ 63 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      - Paris/ Vance, Dec-79/ Feb-80 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      - Parma/ Maggiore '81, 29830 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      - Pearl Necklace/ Eggs/ Silk/ Stone, 38596 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - Pennsylvania, 36770 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      - People, 68/ 76/ 78 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      - People, Nov/1965 - 1967 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      - Personal Eur '88 '89 '84-'89, 1984/ 88 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Perugia, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 71)
      - Pet. Forest (2) Misc. S.W, 31291 (Box 12, Folder 72)
      - Pisa, Apr-70/ Jan-75 (Box 12, Folder 73)
      - Pisa, 31594 (Box 12, Folder 74)
      - Pisa, 31959 (Box 12, Folder 75)
      - Pisa/ Lucca/ Poppi/ Misc. Landscape, 1963/ 70 (Box 12, Folder 76)
      - Pisa Family, Jan-59/ 75 (Box 12, Folder 77)
      - Pistoia, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 78)
      - Pitti Fir. Coradoio, 27851 (Box 12, Folder 79)
      - Plants/ Flowers/ Foil Wrapping X'mas, 2005-2008 (Box 12, Folder 80)
      - Pomodoro, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 81)
      - Pomponio Beach, 10/1/1968 (Box 12, Folder 82)
      - Pontana Fence, Apr-1962 (Box 12, Folder 83)
      - Poppi Castle + Noto Balcony, Feb-1963 (Box 12, Folder 84)
      - Prato - Pugi, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 85)
      - Prato Personal, 27576 (Box 12, Folder 86)
      - Priveto (Personal), 1979 (Box 12, Folder 87)
      - Pred Graphic Design, 1977/ 79/ 83 (Box 12, Folder 88)
      - Perugia, Mar-1963 (Box 12, Folder 89)
      - Pt. Lobos (Miri)/ badger, Feb-1966 (Box 12, Folder 90)
      - Pt. Lobos (Levin) Bill + Anna, Jan-1969 (Box 12, Folder 91)
      - Pt. Lobos (Miri + Lyda) '90, 32874 (Box 12, Folder 92)